moneyduniya.com 2019-02-16

# 

#### Privacy Policy

FACTS | WHAT DOES moneyduniya.com DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?  
---|---  
Why? | Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.  
What? | The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include: 

  * Social Security number
  * Bank account information
  * Employment information
  * Income information
  * Residence, telephone and personal information
  * Pay period information

When you are _no longer_ a customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.  
  
How? | All financial companies need to share consumer' personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their consumers' personal information; the reasons moneyduniya.com chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.  
Reasons we can share your personal information | Does moneyduniya.com share? | Can you limit this sharing?  
---|---|---  
For our everyday business purposes - such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus | Yes | No  
For our marketing purposes - to offer our products and services to you | Yes | No  
For joint marketing with other financial companies | No | N/A  
For our affiliates' everyday business purposes - information about your transactions and experiences | No | N/A  
For our affiliates' everyday business purposes - information about your creditworthiness | No | N/A  
For nonaffiliates to market to you | Yes | No  
Who We Are  
---  
Who is providing this notice? | moneyduniya.com  
What We Do  
---  
How does moneyduniya.com protect my personal information? | To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings. Although our Web site is encrypted to protect your electronic relationship with us, our site contains links to other Web sites, and we are not responsible for their privacy policies.  
How does moneyduniya.com collect my personal information? | We collect your personal information, for example, when you 

  * Apply for a loan

Why can't I limit all sharing? | Federal law gives you the right to limit only 

  * sharing for affiliates' everyday business purposes - information about your creditworthiness
  * affiliates from using your information to market to you
  * sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you

State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing. See below for more on your rights under state law.  
  
Definitions  
---  
Affiliates | Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies. 

Nonaffiliates | Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies. 

Joint Marketing | A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you. 

Other Important Information  
---  
The essence of our business is transmitting your information to, and sharing that information with, nonaffiliate lenders and marketing partners. By using our service, you consent to such sharing, and the receipt of marketing offers. You cannot opt out of such sharing and still use our service. If you do not consent to such sharing, you must discontinue your loan application.
